[
    {
        "level": "1",
        "question": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question_no": 1,
                "question": "What is Noun?",
                "options": [
                    {
                        "opt": "noun is pronoun"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "noun is name"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "noun is article"
                    }
                ],
                "answer": "noun is name"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question_no": 2,
                "question": "Is APPLE a noun?",
                "options": [
                    {
                        "opt": "NO"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "YES"
                    }
                ],
                "answer": "YES"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "level": "2",
        "question": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question_no": 1,
                "question": "What is article?",
                "options": [
                    {
                        "opt": "a"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "and"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "the"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "All of the above"
                    }
                ],
                "answer": "All of the above"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "level": "3",
        "story": "React makes it painless to create interactive UIs. Design simple views for each state in your application, and React will efficiently update and render just the right components when your data changes.Declarative views make your code more predictable and easier to debug."
    },
    {
        "level": "4",
        "question": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question_no": 1,
                "question": "What is Noun?",
                "options": [
                    {
                        "opt": "noun is pronoun"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "noun is name"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "noun is article"
                    }
                ],
                "answer": "noun is name"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question_no": 2,
                "question": "Is APPLE a noun?",
                "options": [
                    {
                        "opt_1": "NO"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "YES"
                    }
                ],
                "answer": "YES"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "level": "5",
        "question": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question_no": 1,
                "question": "What is article?",
                "options": [
                    {
                        "opt": "a"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "and"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "the"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "All of the above"
                    }
                ],
                "answer": "All of the above"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "level": "6",
        "story": "React makes it painless to create interactive UIs. Design simple views for each state in your application, and React will efficiently update and render just the right components when your data changes.Declarative views make your code more predictable and easier to debug."
    },
    {
        "level": "7",
        "question": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question_no": 1,
                "question": "What is Noun?",
                "options": [
                    {
                        "opt": "noun is pronoun"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "noun is name"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "noun is article"
                    }
                ],
                "answer": "noun is name"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question_no": 2,
                "question": "Is APPLE a noun?",
                "options": [
                    {
                        "opt": "NO"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "YES"
                    }
                ],
                "answer": "YES"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "level": "8",
        "question": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question_no": 1,
                "question": "What is article?",
                "options": [
                    {
                        "opt": "a"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "and"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "the"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "All of the above"
                    }
                ],
                "answer": "All of the above"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "level": "9",
        "story": "React makes it painless to create interactive UIs. Design simple views for each state in your application, and React will efficiently update and render just the right components when your data changes.Declarative views make your code more predictable and easier to debug."
    },
    {
        "level": "10",
        "question": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question_no": 1,
                "question": "What is Noun?",
                "options": [
                    {
                        "opt": "noun is pronoun"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "noun is name"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "noun is article"
                    }
                ],
                "answer": "noun is name"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question_no": 2,
                "question": "Is APPLE a noun?",
                "options": [
                    {
                        "opt": "NO"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "YES"
                    }
                ],
                "answer": "YES"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "level": "11",
        "question": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question_no": 1,
                "question": "What is article?",
                "options": [
                    {
                        "opt": "a"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "and"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "the"
                    },
                    {
                        "opt": "All of the above"
                    }
                ],
                "answer": "All of the above"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "level": "12",
        "story": "React makes it painless to create interactive UIs. Design simple views for each state in your application, and React will efficiently update and render just the right components when your data changes.Declarative views make your code more predictable and easier to debug."
    }
]